axial.net 2019-07-16

# Privacy Policy

Updated June 18, 2019

This Privacy Policy explains how Axial Networks, Inc. and its subsidiaries and affiliates (collectively, “Axial”, “we”, “our” and “us”) collects, uses, shares and protects information obtained from members and from visitors to its website, www.axial.net (the “Site”) and the services, features, content, platform, tools or applications we offer (collectively with the Site, the “Services”). If you are a member with access to Axial’s Services, you have agreed and are additionally subject to the Terms of Service, which incorporates this Privacy Policy by reference. By visiting the Site or using the Services, you consent to the collection, disclosure and use of your information under the terms of this Privacy Policy.

## What is the purpose of this Privacy Policy?

When you share information with us, we can make our Services even better by showing you more relevant information and connecting you with others more quickly and easily. As you continue to use our Services, we want you to clearly understand how we are using your information and how you can protect your privacy.

This Privacy Policy is designed to clarify:

  * What information we collect and why we collect it.
  * How we use that information.
  * And the choices you have to access, share and update information.

In order to understand this Privacy Policy, you may want to familiarize yourself (if you haven’t already) with terms like “cookies”, “browsers” and “IP addresses”. As much as possible, we try to communicate with our users in good, plain English.

## What types of information does Axial gather about me?

We collect information in several ways, including:

  * #### Information you submit to us. 

When you sign up for our Services and an account is created (your “Account”), we’ll ask for personal information, including but not limited to your name, email address or telephone number, which may be personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”). If you want to take full advantage of the Services, you’ll also need to create a profile that will be a part of the information submitted to us. By creating an Account on the Services and providing such Personal Information to us, you allow others, including us, to identify you and therefore may not be anonymous. Some features of the Services allow you to provide content to the Services, such as written comments. All content submitted by you to the Services may be retained by us indefinitely, even after you terminate your Account. We may continue to disclose such content to third parties in a manner that does not reveal Personal Information, as described in this Privacy Policy.

  * #### Information we get from your use of our Services

We may collect information about the Services that you use and how you use them, like when you visit a certain part of our Site and how you interact with our content. This information includes:

  * #### Device information

We may collect device-specific information (such as your hardware model, operating system version, unique device identifiers, and mobile network information including phone number). Axial may associate your device identifiers or phone number with your Account.

  * #### Log information

When you use our Services or view content provided by us, we may automatically collect and store certain information in server logs. This may include:

  * Details of how you used our Services, such as your search queries.
  * Internet protocol address.
  * Device event information such as crashes, system activity, hardware settings, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and referral URL.
  * Cookies that may uniquely identify your browser or your Axial Account.
  * Usage information, such as the number and frequency of visitors to the Site.
  * #### Cookies and anonymous identifiers

We use various technologies to collect and store information when you use our Services, and this may include sending one or more cookies or anonymous identifiers to your device or browser. When you visit our website, we send one or more cookies (a small file containing a string of characters) to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. Cookies make it easier for you to log on to and use the Site during future visits. You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. (Each browser is different, so check the “Help” menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.) However, we strongly recommend that you leave cookies active, because they enable you to take advantage the most attractive features of the Services. This Privacy Policy covers our use of cookies only and does not cover the use of cookies by third parties. We do not control when or how third parties place cookies on your computer.

  * #### Email communications

We may receive a confirmation when you open an email from us. We use this confirmation to improve our customer service.

  * #### Aggregate information

We collect statistical information about how both members and visitors, collectively, use the Services (“Aggregate Information”). Some of this information is derived from your Personal Information, but this statistical information is not Personal Information and cannot be tied back to you, your Account or your web browser.

  * #### Financial information

Financial information, such as your payment method (valid credit card number, type, expiration date or other financial information) may be collected and stored by a third party payment processing company (the “Payment Processor”), and use and storage of that information is governed by such Payment Processor’s applicable terms of service and privacy policy.

## How does Axial use my information?

We use the information we collect to provide, maintain, protect and improve our Services, to develop new ones, and to protect Axial and our users.

We use your Personal Information to process and administer details of your membership, to communicate with you, to provide you with opportunities, and to keep you up to date with new developments at Axial.

We also use and analyze the information we collect so that we can administer, support, improve and develop our business. Axial may contact you using information you voluntarily provide. It’s important for you to understand that:

  * Except as set forth herein, we do not share your information with unaffiliated companies for marketing purposes without your prior permission.
  * Unless you opt-out, we may share information about you among companies affiliated with us to inform you about additional products, services or promotions that may be of interest to you.

If you contact us for troubleshooting, we may also keep a record of that fact to better serve you and other Axial customers in the future.

## Disclosure of Your Information

 _Disclosure for our protection or our users’ protection_. Axial is committed to keeping your information confidential. Axial may access, preserve and disclose your Personal Information (a) in response to legal process, (b) to protect our rights, as otherwise required by law or permitted by this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service, including investigations of potential violations hereof, (c) in response to user support requests or (d) for the prevention or detection of a crime.

 _Business transfers_. If we sell our company or any part of it, or our business enters into a joint venture with another business entity, Axial may disclose or transfer your Personal Information to our new business partners or owners who may then provide you with information about their products and services. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of us or our assets may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this policy.

 _Third party disclosures_. Axial does not sell, license, lease or otherwise disclose your information to any third party except as set forth in this policy and as described below:

  * In order to administer or process a transaction, product or the services provided by Axial;
  * To comply with applicable laws, regulation or legal process;
  * To detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud or security issues;
  * We provide information to our agents, affiliates or other trusted businesses or persons to process it for us, based on our instructions and in compliance with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures; and
  * To help us improve our services to you, we may engage another business to help us to carry out certain internal functions such as account processing, fulfillment, member service, member satisfaction surveys or other data collection activities relevant to our business.
  * We share Aggregate Information with our partners, service providers and other persons with whom we conduct business. We share this type of statistical data so that our partners can understand how and how often people use our Services and their services or websites, which facilitates improving both their services and how our Services interface with them. In addition, these third parties may share with us non-private, aggregated or otherwise non-Personal Information about you that they have independently developed or acquired.
  * As stated above, a Payment Processor may collect and store financial information. We may from time to time request and receive some of your financial information for the purposes of completing transactions you have initiated through the Services, enrolling you in discount, rebate, and other programs in which you elect to participate, protecting against or identifying possible fraudulent transactions, and otherwise as needed to manage our business.

## Additional Limits on Use of Your Google User Data

Notwithstanding anything else in this Privacy Policy, if you provide the App access to the following types of your Google data, the App's use of that data will be subject to these additional restrictions:

  * Axial Services will only use access to read, write, modify, or control Gmail message bodies (including attachments), metadata, headers, and settings to provide a web email client that allows users to compose, send, read, and process emails and will not transfer this Gmail data to others unless doing so is necessary to provide and improve these features, comply with applicable law, or as part of a merger, acquisition, or sale of assets.
  * Axial Services will not use this Gmail data for serving advertisements.
  * Axial Services will not allow humans to read this data unless we have your affirmative agreement for specific messages, doing so is necessary for security purposes such as investigating abuse, to comply with applicable law, or for the App's internal operations and even then only when the data have been aggregated and anonymized.

## Can I opt-out of Axial’s collection and use of information?

Yes, but we require a minimum amount of information from you in order to provide our product and services. By withholding certain information from us, you may limit your ability to use our Services in whole or part.

## Security & Information Retention

We employ security measures to protect your Personal Information both online and offline from access by unauthorized persons and against unlawful processing, accidental loss, destruction and damage. We encrypt many of our services using SSL. We will retain your Personal Information for a reasonable period or as long as the law requires. If you cease to be a member of Axial, we may retain your Personal Information for our business purposes provided that we will protect all such information about you in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

## What risks do I take by sharing information?

Although we allow you to set privacy options that limit access to your personal information, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We cannot guarantee that only authorized persons will view your personal information. We cannot ensure that information you share on our website will not become publicly available. We are not responsible for third party circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures on our website. You can reduce these risks by using common sense security practices such as choosing a strong password and using up to date antivirus software.

## Third Party Sites

We are not responsible for the practices, privacy policies or the content of third party sites, services and applications (“Third Party Services”) we link to or you elect to access through the Services, and have no control of the use or protection of information provided by you to or collected by those Third Party Services. Whenever you choose to access a Third Party Service, you may be asked to provide registration or other information. Please note that the information you are providing is going to a third-party, and you should familiarize yourself with the privacy policy provided by that party.

## What Information of Mine Can I Access?

If you are a member, you can access information associated with your Account by logging into the Services. Members and visitors can access and delete cookies through their web browser settings.

 _California Privacy Rights_ : Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice identifying the categories of personal customer information which we share with our affiliates and/or third parties for marketing purposes, and providing contact information for such affiliates and/or third parties. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the following address: 902 Broadway, 19th Floor, New York, NY 10010.

## How Can I Delete My Account?

Should you ever decide to delete your Account, you may do so by emailing privacy@axial.net. If you terminate your Account, any association between your Account and information we store will no longer be accessible through your Account.

## Changes to This Policy

Axial may update this policy from time to time. Any changes to this Privacy Policy in the future will be indicated on the Site. Your continued use of the Site and, if you are a member, your continued participation in Axial, will indicate your agreement to such changes. If you would like to see the prior versions of this Privacy Policy, please contact us via the email address below.

## What should I do if I have more questions?

All comments, queries and requests relating to our use of your personal information are welcomed and should be addressed to the e-mail address privacy@axial.net.
